So this is a test video. This sample
video has been made with
DaVinci Resolve, and currently,
I am reading from a pre-written script
that was actually written
before this video was ever
constructed. Along with this video, you
will notice several random
images picked from my own
personal library to showcase all the
different functionalities
that DaVinci Resolve can do.
DaVinci Resolve is a robust and
fascinating video editor
capable of many different feats,
such as color grading, advanced editing,
as well as other amazing and simple
techniques that anyone
can use. It doesn't matter if you're a
newer video editor or if
you're much more experienced.
DaVinci Resolve, while it is free, can
provide you all of these things at the
simple touch of a button.